{"$type":"System.Collections.Generic.List`1[[Milionar.Answers, Milionar]], mscorlib","$values":[{"$type":"Milionar.Answers, Milionar","Question":"Jake je pocasi?","Answer":{"$type":"System.Collections.Generic.List`1[[System.String, mscorlib]], mscorlib","$values":["ano","slunicko","pekne nahovno","prosil bych bez cibule"]},"Good":0},{"$type":"Milionar.Answers, Milionar","Question":"Jak se máš?","Answer":{"$type":"System.Collections.Generic.List`1[[System.String, mscorlib]], mscorlib","$values":["Vážně","mě","to","nezajímá"]},"Good":0},{"$type":"Milionar.Answers, Milionar","Question":"wow","Answer":{"$type":"System.Collections.Generic.List`1[[System.String, mscorlib]], mscorlib","$values":["k1","k2","k3","k4"]},"Good":0},{"$type":"Milionar.Answers, Milionar","Question":"jees","Answer":{"$type":"System.Collections.Generic.List`1[[System.String, mscorlib]], mscorlib","$values":["okuj","jtzj","toop","weee"]},"Good":0},{"$type":"Milionar.Answers, Milionar","Question":"wef","Answer":{"$type":"System.Collections.Generic.List`1[[System.String, mscorlib]], mscorlib","$values":["fwe","wef","gerge","gerger"]},"Good":0},{"$type":"Milionar.Answers, Milionar","Question":"gerge","Answer":{"$type":"System.Collections.Generic.List`1[[System.String, mscorlib]], mscorlib","$values":["gerge","greger","egg","eer"]},"Good":0},{"$type":"Milionar.Answers, Milionar","Question":"qweq","Answer":{"$type":"System.Collections.Generic.List`1[[System.String, mscorlib]], mscorlib","$values":["wefw","fwe","fwef","re"]},"Good":0},{"$type":"Milionar.Answers, Milionar","Question":"rreeeeee","Answer":{"$type":"System.Collections.Generic.List`1[[System.String, mscorlib]], mscorlib","$values":["gege","rrr","ewwe","rewwe"]},"Good":0},{"$type":"Milionar.Answers, Milionar","Question":"werwe","Answer":{"$type":"System.Collections.Generic.List`1[[System.String, mscorlib]], mscorlib","$values":["werw","eere","rrre","trtrtr"]},"Good":0},{"$type":"Milionar.Answers, Milionar","Question":"ererge","Answer":{"$type":"System.Collections.Generic.List`1[[System.String, mscorlib]], mscorlib","$values":["qwdq","qwqwd","sad","qwdqwq"]},"Good":0},{"$type":"Milionar.Answers, Milionar","Question":"qwdqwdq","Answer":{"$type":"System.Collections.Generic.List`1[[System.String, mscorlib]], mscorlib","$values":["qwdq","fwefwef","gerg","wqewe"]},"Good":0},{"$type":"Milionar.Answers, Milionar","Question":"wefwe","Answer":{"$type":"System.Collections.Generic.List`1[[System.String, mscorlib]], mscorlib","$values":["wefwe","gerger","rth","hrth"]},"Good":0},{"$type":"Milionar.Answers, Milionar","Question":"wefw","Answer":{"$type":"System.Collections.Generic.List`1[[System.String, mscorlib]], mscorlib","$values":["ewwefwe","qwdqwe","wefwe","egrger"]},"Good":0},{"$type":"Milionar.Answers, Milionar","Question":"gerge","Answer":{"$type":"System.Collections.Generic.List`1[[System.String, mscorlib]], mscorlib","$values":["qweqwe","qweqw","wewe","rewr"]},"Good":0},{"$type":"Milionar.Answers, Milionar","Question":"rewrerw","Answer":{"$type":"System.Collections.Generic.List`1[[System.String, mscorlib]], mscorlib","$values":["werwe","gerge","gerg","werwerwer"]},"Good":0}]}